businessownersideacafe.com 2019-03-18

# Business Owners' Idea Cafe - Our Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy for Business Owners Idea Cafe

**Privacy Notice**

DevStart is an online network of websites for small business owners.  Headquartered  in Chicago, Illinois, we provide websites relating to marketing, search engine optimization, web hosting, small business operations, and website development.  We are committed to maintaining the trust and confidence of our visitors to our web site and subscribers to our newsletters. Here you’ll find information on how we treat data that we collect from visitors to our website, or when someone subscribes to our newsletter.

**Visitors to our Website**

When someone visits a site on our network, we use a third party service, Google Analytics, to collect standard internet log information and details of visitor behavior patterns. We do this to find out things such as the number of visitors to the various parts of the site. This information is only processed in a way which does not identify anyone. We do not make, and do not allow Google to make, any attempt to find out the identities of those visiting our website. You can find more information on how cookies are used on this website in the Cookies Policy.

If we do want to collect personally identifiable information through our website, we will be up front about this. We will make it clear when we collect personal information and will explain what we intend to do with it.

**Newsletter Sign Up**

As part of the registration process for our e-newsletter at Idea Café, HostReview, and PromotionWorld, we collect personal information. We use that information for a few reasons: to tell you about stuff you’ve asked us to tell you about; to contact you if we need to obtain or provide additional information; to check our records are right and to check every now and then that you’re happy and satisfied. We don't share or trade email lists with other organizations and businesses.

We use a third party provider, MailChimp, to deliver our newsletter. We gather statistics around email opening and clicks using industry standard technologies to help us monitor and improve our e-newsletter. For more information, please see [MailChimp’s privacy notice](https://mailchimp.com/legal/privacy/).

You can unsubscribe to general mailings at any time of the day or night by clicking the unsubscribe link at the bottom of any of our emails.

**Links to Other Web Sites**

This privacy notice does not cover the links within this site linking to other websites. Those sites are not governed by this Privacy Policy, and if you have questions about how a site uses your information, you’ll need to check that site’s privacy statement.

**Access to Your Personal Information**

You have a right to (1) access, modify, correct, or delete certain of your information regarding your user profile, and (2) close your account. You can also contact us regarding any account information which is not on your profile or readily accessible to you. If you close your account, your information may be removed or unpublished from the Services within a reasonable amount of time.  Email your request to [privacy@devstart.com](mailto:privacy@devstart.com).

Once you submit a review and the review has been approved for posting, it cannot be edited or removed.  You will have the ability to submit a revision to appear below your original posting and to revise your star ratings.

We keep your account information for as long as your account is active or as needed. For example, we may keep certain information even after you close your account if it is necessary to comply with our legal obligations, meet regulatory requirements, resolve disputes, prevent fraud and abuse, enforce our agreements or as part of our Website data backup process. We may keep your data in a published or unpublished format on the Services or in backups of the Website.

**CHILDREN**

Our Websites and/or Services are not directed at children and our services are designed for businesses. We do not knowingly collect information from or about children under 13 years of age, and use of our services by children under 13 years of age is forbidden.

**Security**

We have implemented various technical, administrative, and physical safeguards to protect your information. These safeguards vary depending on the sensitivity of the information at issue.

**Changes to this Privacy Notice**

We keep our privacy notice under regular review. This privacy notice was last updated on May 25, 2018.

**CONTACT US**

If you have any questions or concerns over this Privacy Policy, or wish to exercise any of your statutory rights, please contact us at:

DevStart, Inc. Privacy Matters  
c/o DevStart, Inc.  
Attn: Director of Security  
64 Orland Square Drive  
Suite 314A  
Orland Park, IL 60462  
USA

Email – [privacy@devstart.com](mailto:privacy@devstart.com)

Back to Registration Form  |  Back to Idea Cafe Home
